FROM ME TO YOU 2ND SEASON
I'm heading out!
Have a nice day!
This April...
We became 2nd year students.
2ND-YEAR STUDENTS
24. SAWAKO KURONUMA
What about everyone else?
Sa... wa... ko!
Hi- yah!
Just two more years 'til
graduation! Let's have fun!
I'm surprised! A lot of
us got clumped together.
Yeah, we seriously lucked out!
We did!
Uh-huh! Tomo and Ekko
ended up in our class.
Joe too.
- And you're his favorite! OM chuckle
- Oh, lucky me.
If we were separated... I'm sure I would
have been way too lonely... This is a dream.
I mean, I guess? Uh huh...
We got put in the same class, so this
year's gonna be a little different. -Then
I'll just have to bring
the CD tomorrow... -G- Good...
- Good...
- Oh, she's really going for it.
Morning!
Morning.
Hey guys! This girl here's Sawako
Kuronuma. You can call her Sadako if you
want. Treat her nice!
By the looks of it,
everything's still exactly the same.
Yo! All of you! Opening
ceremony! Line up in the hallway.
Ryu, same class, isn't that great?
And I even had a dream
where I was going out with her!
Huh... No way...?
So, I went and saw Akihiko's
concert and it was so awesome!
- Wow!
- Hey! Kids in the back, snuggle up. Okay?!
- Apparently Chigusa's in Class C.
- Oh, so that's where she ended up.
Man, don't'cha think it's wild we
all ended up in the same class again?
Yeah, totally. So wild.
Huh? What're you actin' all smug for?
More importantly though...
What?! You didn't give him the chocolates?
You had them prepared
and everything. Why, not?
I knew it. Something
happened on Valentine's Day.
She's been super awkward
with him ever since then.
Well, it could also mean she's finally
started to take him seriously as a guy
though. Still...
What the heck are those two doing?! -They
had spring break and other holidays, so
many chances! -Hey... You okay?
Sawako... love is all about timing, okay?
It's Kurumi.
I was already flat out rejected... so...
He won't accept chocolates
from someone who likes him.
Ever since that day, it's
always... always been on my mind.
Does that mean... Kazehaya has
no intention of dating anyone?
Please face both sports and academics
seriously, with a firm resolve. -Or maybe...
could it be... that he already has someone
he likes? -As for the current students,
make sure to welcome the newcomers with
open arms... They'll be counting on you to
show them the way, so be kind.
I think... I finally understand why
Kurumi wanted him to just be "everyone's
Kazehaya"...
Are you sure there's not a
deeper meaning... if there's a chance?
I was able to be in the same class as him.
He would even say, "Good morning," to me.
Those things alone
have felt like a dream.
But... I couldn't forget the time
we spent together. I wanted more...
Could it be... I am just being greedy?
And that's my ulterior motive?
Akihiko's catchphrase was totally
awesome to hear in person! Man, I wish you
could've been there with me, you know?
- Hey wait, it's Sadako... isn't it?
- You know me?
Well, that must mean we're neighbors! So
pleased to make your acquaintance! Oh, and
- my name is Kento Miura!
- Y-yeah, same here. Nice to meet you.
Hi! Okay!
Wait, is he for real??
Look at that. Nice eyebrows. Heh!
So close.
Hey, what's up with the scary face you're
making? You should work on reelin' it back
a little bit. A girl shouldn't be
frowning like that! Boop, boop. Boop,
- boop.
- I... I wasn't expecting that.
Okay then, we're gonna randomly choose
all the class roles and stuff real quick.
First off, for the class rep, we'll have...
So that's how it is. My choice. Huh?
This little piggy went to market, this
little piggy stayed home, this little
piggy ate roast beef and this little
piggy had none... almost there... and this
- little piggy is gonna be our class re...
- This is no time to freeze
- up. Everyone's stressed out... I...
- Oh! I guess I'm the man for the job.
That was close! I almost stole
somebody's fun away from them!
What?! You are seriously volunteering?
- This way I can stand out.
- Don't worry, no matter what ya do,
you'll never stand out more than me.
That guy seems... like he's
gonna be a real character.
New species?
Um. For campus life rep, I'd
like to nominate Kuronuma.
She's great at taking care of the
flowers. So I think it's a good fit.
But I didn't really -
You always did it.
Watered the flowers and stuff.
And you both noticed?
That makes me so happy.
Thanks so much.
Wow...
What's up?
She can smile.
- But if it's too much work, I'll help.
- Thanks, I'd really like that!
Next up, the disciplinary rep
will be... Jonouchi! Congratulations!
All rise. Bow.
Good work!
- Oh yeah, that sounds good to me too--
- Hey, Miura!
What?
Lemme borrow you a sec. -Since you're the
class rep now, it's important for me to
teach you the ropes as well as how
to respect your teacher. -Yes, sir!
Ugh, well that sounds like a pain in the
butt. And that's why you don't sign up for
- these things.
- But the challenge is
what's good about it.
I see you're as optimistic as ever.
Oh hey, Tsuru!
Feel free to go home without me, kay?
Wha... Uhh obviously I'm
not gonna wait that long.
Then we should all go
and hang out somewhere.
I'm down. Then Okamoto, you pick a place.
- Bye! I'll see you guys tomorrow!
- Later!
Take care!
Alright, I guess that's my cue to head to
the library. You do your best too, okay?
I will.
Exactly! The whole
thing is just hilarious!
Kazehaya...
- Kuronuma, Heading home?
- Uh. I'm staying after a little, to
- plant some seeds in the flower bed.
- I see.
Kazehaya?
Yeah! Later then.
B- Bye.
Goodbye.
Sorry.
Actually, you go without me.
Hey! Ryu!
Is practice already
starting for you guys?
Uh-huh.
So, have they set a date already?
A date for what?
- Um, for Toru's wedding ceremony!
- Ah... When was that?
I think... it'll be soon.
I guess I'm just gonna have to ask Pops.
- Good morning!
Hey. Sup?
- Oh, that's right, you have a game soon.
- We're about to start the
spring Hokkaido tournament.
- If you win, you go to Koshien?
- That's in the summer. For spring, it's
like a tournament to test your strength.
- Anyway. you just gotta win it, don't'cha?
- For sure.
See ya.
Mmhm! I'll come by to
eat some ramen tonight!
Uhh...
- Thank you for doing that thing for me.
- Huh? What thing?
You know what I mean. The class
arrangement. Remember? I asked you to take
care of those special requests?
Nahhh. Why would I bother
listening to every one of those things?
Huh? Wait, so you didn't?
During your 2nd and 3rd year of high
school, there are a ton of events that
happen. And it's meant to be the
most fun time in your entire life.
It's a simple matter of human nature to
not want to separate those who've already
- proven that they along with one another.
- Human nature? -Anyway, that's what this
incredibly handsome teacher I happen to
know was explaining to me!
Handsome?
You can tell how close they are by
observing. Just watch over them for a year
- and it becomes obvious.
- Uh, you haven't even been
our teacher for a ye-- Huh?
And that incredibly handsome teacher
happens to be the one and only Kazuichi
Arai. The very man who's destined
to become president in the future!
I'm going home. I wasted
both my time and chocolates.
You really are a tight knit group.
So, make sure, you
enjoy these next two years.
La la la La la la La la la...
Well, you just ruined a beautiful moment...
Well, that's unexpected.
- You still haven't gone home, huh?
- No.
Ahaaaa...
Kazehaya, why do you
still not have a girlfriend?
You're pretty popular with all the girls,
so I'm curious. Oh! Is it that you like
someone? I bet you do! You do, right?
- Have you ever heard of boundaries before?
- Who is it? If it's
anyone I know, I could help.
Yano, this isn't like you at all.
I don't need anyone to help me.
Besides...
If I admitted to liking someone, i'd want
that person to be the first to know. So, I
couldn't tell you.
Ugh... it's no use.
He's the type to get super pissed if a
third party tries to get up in his
business. Well, when it comes down to
it, it is their own problem to sort out...
And if the timing doesn't
match up for them in the end...
Then that'll be that.
This'll be... the herb corner.
Is she... a witch?
All done!
I didn't think he was still here.
Did you plant a lot of seeds?
Uh Yeah.
I thought he went home already...
What should I do? I
feel like I can't breathe.
It's been so long... since
we've been alone together...
Wait, how did I used to talk to
him during moments like this?
We got to be in the same class.
I'm so glad.
He smiled.
Though when our seats are
far, we can't talk as much.
Y-Yeah.
Could it be that... he
was worrying about me?
We're together until graduation.
But what makes me... even happier... is
the fact... that I'll be able to stay by
Kazehaya's side until graduation.
And I want that more than ever.
Were you waiting for someone?
Yeah. You, Kuronuma.
I stayed here. To see you.
You know, I always assumed At least out
of all the other guys in class, I was the
one who was by far the closest
with you. But maybe I was wrong?
Was I... being too full of myself?
The closest...
Uh... th... uh...
Well, it's... uh... Uh...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
Of course saying something like that out
of nowhere would make you upset, right?
No...
See ya.
That's not it.
That isn't how I feel.
It's hard... because no matter how I
respond... no matter what words I use... I
know there will be a
special meaning behind it.
An unexpected combo.
The smile that was once all mine...
Distant, yet unchanged from before...
Next time: "Forget What I Said"